hostseeq.com 2005-03-23

# HostSeeq - Privacy Policy

**Hosting Provider Fusepoint Registers Positive EBITDA**

Fusepoint Managed Services ([www.fusepoint.com](http://www.fusepoint.com/)), a provider of managed application and web hosting services, announced it has registered positive earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) for the first time in the company’s history. According to Fusepoint, its revenue grew 115 percent in 2003... 

**MyPhotoAlbum to Host Tradeshow Images**

FortuneCity ([www.fortunecity.com](http://www.fortunecity.com/)), a provider of web hosting services, announced on September 30, 2004 that its MyPhotoAlbum photo hosting service has entered into partnership agreements with DigitalLife Tradeshow and the Adventures in Travel Expo to become the exclusive online photo provider to the shows, which are projected...

**HostSeeq Privacy Policy**

HostSeeq obeys a strict code of privacy in regards to our customers' and visitors' information. The following outlines what information we collect, and what we will do with it. HostSeeq is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

**Registration**  
If you wish to download software, make a purchase, participate in a contest, or receive information, we will ask you to register. During registration you will be required to provide your contact information (such as name and email address). 

**Order**  
We request information from you to process your order. Here you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch you. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**   
We do not share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use identifiable information for any secondary purposes. The security staff of this website takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry. 

**SSL.**  
While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Netscape and Microsoft IE web browsers become locked, as opposed to unlocked / open when you are just surfing. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

Credit card numbers stored in our database are encrypted for your protection. This data appears as illegible characters and is not stored as clear text. 

**Special Offers**  
We send all new customers and registered visitors a welcoming email to verify their selections. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we do offer our customers the option to not receive these types of communications. 

**Site and Service Updates**  
We also send our customers product announcement updates. Customers are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the products they use. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in reference to issues relating to their account via email or or direct mail. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a chance to inform us that we can't use their information. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy in place when the information was collected.
